sitesdoneright.com 2001-12-20

# sites-done-right.com - Chicago webmasters design firm small business

**_OVERVIEW_**

Webmaster, Inc. may ask you to register and provide information that personally identifies you ("Personal Information") in certain circumstances (e.g., when you sign up to be on our emailing list to receive our newsletters). We use your Personal Information for three primary purposes: 

> To help you quickly find services or information on SITES-DONE-RIGHT.COM. 
> 
> To help us display the Web site content most relevant to your areas of interest. 
> 
> To alert you to product upgrades, special offers, updated information and other new services from Webmaster, Inc. 

If you choose not to register and provide Personal Information, you can still use most of the SITES-DONE-RIGHT.COM site. However, you will not be able to access areas that require registration.

Webmaster, Inc. does not provide your Personal Information to third parties. If you do not want Webmaster, Inc. to send you e-mail or postal mail regarding SITES-DONE-RIGHT.COM products or services, you may opt out when you give us your Personal Information (by selecting the option stating that you do not wish to receive such marketing materials from SITES-DONE-RIGHT.COM). Where opting out of receiving e-mail or postal mail regarding SITES-DONE-RIGHT.COM products or services does not make sense (for example a product request form), opting out will not be possible. 

If you begin a registration form, then decide you don't want to finish it, just click the reset button on the bottom of the page. You may then use the navigation buttons in your browser, or enter a web address manually. None of the information entered on the page where you quit will be saved. However, information entered on previous pages (if applicable) may be saved. 

If for some reason you believe SITES-DONE-RIGHT.COM has not adhered to these principles, please notify us by e-mail at [webmaster@sites-done-right.com](mailto:webmaster@sites-done-right.com), and we will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and correct the problem.

* * *

* * *

Copyright © Webmaster, Inc. All Rights Reserved  
This site is optimized for 24-bit color at 800x600 resolution.  
Read our Privacy Policy
